# 1
p "Question 1 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "Assign the variable x to the",
	answer_1: "x == 5",
	answer_2: "5 == x",
	answer_3: "x = 5",
	answer_4: "5 = x",
	correct: 3,
	question_2: "value of 5"
	)
# 2
p "Question 2 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "What does this expression evaluate to?",
	answer_1: "YOLO",
	answer_2: '"YO" + "LO"',
	answer_3: "YOLO",
	answer_4: "YO + LO",
	correct: 1,
	question_2: '"YO" + "LO"'
	)
# 3
p "Question 3 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "What is the datatype of",
	answer_1: "String",
	answer_2: "Word",
	answer_3: "Integer",
	answer_4: "Float",
	correct: 1,
	question_2: '"Matt"'
	)
# 4
p "Question 4 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "What is the datatype of",
	answer_1: "String",
	answer_2: "Number",
	answer_3: "Integer",
	answer_4: "Float",
	correct: 2,
	question_2: "5"
	)
# 5
p "Question 5 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "What does this expression evaluate to?",
	answer_1: "bob42",
	answer_2: '"bob"42',
	answer_3: '"bob" + 42',
	answer_4: "error",
	correct: 4,
	question_2: '"bob" + 42'
	)
# 6
p "Question 6 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "What does the following expression evaluate to?",
	answer_1: "34",
	answer_2: "7",
	answer_3: "3 + 4",
	answer_4: "3,4",
	correct: 2,
	question_2: "3 + 4"
	)
# 7
p "Question 7 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "What does the following expression evaluate to?",
	answer_1: "1.5",
	answer_2: "1,5",
	answer_3: "error",
	answer_4: "1",
	correct: 4,
	question_2: "3/2"
	)
# 8
p "Question 8 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "What does the following expression evaluate to?",
	answer_1: "Lisbon",
	answer_2: "l + i + s + b + o + n",
	answer_3: "LisboN",
	answer_4: "LISBON",
	correct: 4,
	question_2: '"lisbon".upcase'
	)
# 9
p "Question 9 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "What is the problem with the following code?",
	answer_1: "You should not have a comma inside the double quotes",
	answer_2: "The equal sign should be ==",
	answer_3: "The order should be reversed",
	answer_4: "The order should be reversed	You should not have blank spaces when declaring a variable",
	correct: 4,
	question_2: 'my variable = "I,m cool"'
	)
# 10
p "Question 10 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "Make the code run well",
	answer_1: 'band == "Blink" + 182',
	answer_2: '"Blink" + 182 == band',
	answer_3: 'band = "Blink" + 182.to_s',
	answer_4: 'band == "Blink" + 182.to_s',
	correct: 3,
	question_2: 'band = "Blink" + 182'
	)
# 11
p "Question 11 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: 'Convert every letter of "YoLo BrAh" to lowercase.',
	answer_1: "nice.each do |word| word.down end",
	answer_2: "nice.each do |word| word.downcase end",
	answer_3: "nice.downcase()",
	answer_4: "nice.Downcase",
	correct: 3,
	question_2: 'nice = "YoLo BrAh"'
	)
# 12
p "Question 12 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "Create an array with",
	answer_1: "{}",
	answer_2: "[]",
	answer_3: "()",
	answer_4: '||',
	correct: 2,
	question_2: "nothing inside it"
	)
# 13
p "Question 13 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "Create an Array that contains the values",
	answer_1: '{"mike tyson", 89, 9.7}',
	answer_2: '["mike tyson", 89, 9.7]',
	answer_3: "[mike tyson, 89, 9.7]",
	answer_4: "(mike tyson, 89, 9.7)",
	correct: 2,
	question_2: '"mike tyson", 89, and 9.7.'
	)
# 14
p "Question 14 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "What does the following expression evaluate to?",
	answer_1: "yes",
	answer_2: "no",
	answer_3: "true",
	answer_4: "false",
	correct: 4,
	question_2: "4 != 4"
	)
# 15
p "Question 15 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "What does the following expression evaluate to?",
	answer_1: "yes",
	answer_2: "no",
	answer_3: "true",
	answer_4: "false",
	correct: 3,
	question_2: "5 > 4"
	)
# 16
p "Question 16 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "What is the value of x when x = 5 and",
	answer_1: "6",
	answer_2: "5",
	answer_3: "5+1",
	answer_4: "5x",
	correct: 1,
	question_2: "x = x + 1"
	)
# 17
p "Question 17 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "What does the following expression return:",
	answer_1: '["uno,dos,tres"]',
	answer_2: '"uno,dos,tres"',
	answer_3: '"uno","dos","tres"',
	answer_4: "3",
	correct: 4,
	question_2: '["uno", "dos", "tres"].length()'
	)
# 18
p "Question 18 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "Get the first element of the lyric Array.",
	answer_1: "lyric.start",
	answer_2: "lyric{1}",
	answer_3: "lyric[0]",
	answer_4: "lyric[1]",
	correct: 3,
	question_2: 'lyric = ["laughter", "its", "free"]'
	)
# 19
p "Question 19 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "Get the last element of the lyric Array.",
	answer_1: "lyric.pop",
	answer_2: "lyric[2]",
	answer_3: "lyric[3]",
	answer_4: "lyric{3}",
	correct: 2,
	question_2: 'lyric = ["laughter", "its", "free"]'
	)
# 20
p "Question 20 Created"
Quiz.create(
	question: "How do you print out",
	answer_1: "Print Hello + World",
	answer_2: 'Print "Hello + World"',
	answer_3: 'p "Hello World"',
	answer_4: 'say "Hello World"',
	correct: 3,
	question_2: '"Hello World"'
	)